瑞秋  履历表快用完了
Rachel. We're running low on resumes.
你真想到 《大众机械》杂志社上班吗
You want a job with Popular Mechanics?
如果你想要从事机械行业
Well, if you're gonna work for mechanics,
那你就算找对地方了
those are the ones to work for.
各位  我什么都得试试
Guys, I'm going for anything here.
我不能再当服务生了
I can't be a waitress anymore.
我是说真的  我已厌倦微薄小费
I mean it. I'm sick of the lousy tips.
我已厌倦顾客不把我当人使唤
I'm sick of being called "Excuse Me."
瑞秋  这些你校对过吗
Rach, did you proofread these?
对  有问题吗
Yeah. Why?
没事  他们对你高超的
Nothing. I'm sure they'll be impressed
"电恼"技术定会印象深刻的
with your excellent "compuper" skills.
糟了  每一份上面都这样吗
Oh, my God! Do you think it's on all of them?
没事  我肯定富士施乐打印机改掉一些了
No, I'm sure the Xerox machine caught a few.
-嗨  小伙子们  -嗨
- Hey, guys. - Hey.
嗨  姑娘们
Hi, ladies.
需要什么吗
Can I get you anything?
信件带来了没
Did you bring the mail?
-很多回复  -真的吗
- Lots of responses. - Really?
我们这儿当然还有烤饼
Sure, we have scones left!
快念给我听
Read them to me.
"亲爱的格林小姐
"Dear Miss Greene:
感谢您的申请  然而..."
Thank you for your inquiry. "However"
-我们有苹果肉桂  -"亲爱的格林小姐"
- We have apple cinnamon -"Dear Ms. Greene...."
好  好  不行
Yeah, yeah! No.
-怎么了  -你的信用卡账单不少呀
- What? - Your Visa bill is huge!
给我
Give me that.
我真不敢相信  琳达那么好
I can't believe you. Linda's so great.
你为何不再和她约会
Why won't you go out with her?
-我也不知道  -还是因为她说了
- I don't know. - ls this still about her...
《摩登原始人》里的情节真有可能发生
... "The Flintstones could have really happened" thing?
不仅仅是那样  我要一个能让我有感觉
It's not just that. I want someone who does something for me...
能让我心跳加速
...who gets my heart pounding.
能给我...
Who makes me....
做小毛绒玩具吗
Little playthings with yarn?
什么
What?
你是有多喜欢她
Could you want her more?
谁
Who?
阿蒂  《发生何事》中那个犀利的妹妹
Dee, the sarcastic sister from What's Happening!!.
我早就不喜欢她了
Look, I'm totally over her.
-嗨  -要咖啡吗
- Hi! - Coffee?
-不用加  -好的
- No, we're fine. - Okay.
-闭嘴  -我们什么都没说
- Shut up! - We're not saying anything.
-怎么了  -昨晚乔伊哭了
- What? - Joey cried last night.
-谢谢  -我们正在玩扑克牌
- Thank you. - We were playing poker
三点上有巧克力  看起来像是八点
There was chocolate on the three. It looked like an eight.
可惜你没看到
You should have seen him.
他说"准备痛哭流涕吧"
"Read them and weep!"
结果哭的是他
And then he did.
你们怎么没和我们玩过扑克牌
Now, how come you guys have never played poker with us?
对啊  为什么
Yeah, what is that?
这是性别歧视的问题吗
Like some kind of sexist guy thing?
这是扑克  只有男人才能玩
It's poker, so only guys can play?
不啊  女生也欢迎加人
No. Women can play.
那么为什么...这到底是为什么
Then, what is it? Some kind of, like, some kind of, you know
快说  到底为什么
All right, what is it?
只是刚好女生没加入罢了
There are just no women in our game.
对  我们刚好找不到会玩扑克的女生
We just don't know any women who know how to play poker.
这个借口真烂  男生都是这种反应
That is such a lame excuse. It's a typical guy response.
请问你们谁会玩扑克牌
Do you know how to play?
不会
No.
-但你们可以教我们  -不要
- But you could teach us. - No.
现在开始抽牌
Okay, so now we draw cards.
我不需要对吧  因为我一把顺
So I wouldn't need any. I have a straight.
-你太棒了  -恭喜了
- Oh, good for you! - Congratulations!
-菲比  你要几张  -我需要两张
- Pheebs, how many do you want? - I just need two.
黑桃十和梅花六
The 10 of spades and the 6 of clubs.
菲比  不  你不能这么要
Pheebs. No, you can't
等等  我有你要的黑桃十  给
Wait! I have the 10 of spades! Here.
谢谢!
Thanks!
不  你不能那样
No, you can't do that.
没关系  我不需要  我要四张同点
It's ok. Don't need them. I'm going for fours.
哦  是吗
Oh, you're.
开始吧
Here we go.
我们有炸鲑鱼圈配蔬菜沙拉
We've got salmon roulettes and assorted crudites.
莫妮卡  你在干什么
Monica. What are you doing?
这是打扑克  食物名称不能超过两个字
This is a poker game. You can't serve food with more than one syllable.
得是薯片  沙司  百奇之类的
It's got to be like chips or dip or pretz.
现在发牌的人...
OK, so at this point, the dealer...
我们会了  开始玩真的吧
We got it. Let's play for real.
高赌资  大笔钱
High stakes. Big bucks!
你当真  菲比刚丢出一双十一点
You sure? Phoebe just threw away two jacks
就因为他们好像不开心
because they didn't look happy.
但我准备好了  发牌吧
But I'm ready. So just deal.
各位  最后通知  乔伊
Okay, last-minute lesson! Joey....
三点
Three.
八点
Eight.
八点  三点  好的  不错
Eight. Three. All right, very good.
该死  该死  该死
Damn it, damn it, damn it!
-我明白了  你们在骗人  -骗什么
- I see, so you were lying. - About what?
-骗你们牌有多好  -那是唬人
- About how good your cards were. - I was bluffing.
什么是唬
And what is bluffing?
不就是骗的同义字吗
Is it not another word for lying?
抱歉  我不能再玩了
Sorry to break up this party,
我得在明天工作前打好履历表
but I've got to go fax resumes before work.
-瑞秋  我们得算帐  -什么定居
- We've got to settle. - Settle what?
在维吉尼亚的詹姆斯敦殖民地
The Jamestown colony of Virginia.
乔治三世把它给了我们美国所以...
See, King George is giving us the land....
-是扑克  瑞秋  你欠我们钱  -对哦
-The game, Rachel. You owe us money. - Right.
这样吧  兄弟们  这是她们第一次打扑克
You know what, you guys? It's their first time,
别和她们计较钱了
why don't we just forget about the money, alright?
那怎么行  我们会付钱的
Hell, no. We'll pay!
莫妮卡  我本来准备好另一个回复了
Monica, I had another answer all ready.
你们知道吗  我们要重来一盘
And you know what? We want a rematch.
我无所谓  钱多不嫌烧手
Well that's fine with me. Could use the money.
这么说你们的组合家具基本上
So basically, you get your ya-yas
都是用朋友的钱买来的
by taking money from your friends.
没错  而且我是在"宜家"家具商场买的
Yes, and I get my ya-yas from IKEA.
得自己动手装  但便宜一点
You have to put them together yourself, but they cost a little less.
瑞秋  这是扑克牌  玩就是要赢
Look, Rach, this is poker. I play to win.
如果我想赢  就得有人输
For me to win, others have to lose.
如果想和我玩牌  就别指望我做个好人
If you're gonna play pocker with me, don't expect me to be a nice guy.
因为牌一发出
Because once those cards are dealt....
然后呢
Yeah?
我就不是个好人
I'm not a nice guy.
各位  吃吧
All right, boys, let's eat.
这是从"我爱瑞秋披萨屋"买的吗
Did you get that from the "I Love Rachel Pizzeria"?
还没笑够啊
You still on that?
得了吧  不然你为何学黑道电影讲话
Come on. What was with that Black Bart speech?
"玩起牌来  我就不是个好人"
"When I play poker, I'm not a nice guy."
你扯太远了
You're way off.
我可不这么认为  因为我觉得你爱她
No, I don't think so, because I think you love her!
不  或许我曾对她有爱意
No. I might have had feelings for her at one time.
但我已心灰意冷
Not anymore.
我只是
I just
马塞尔  你拿那张光盘要干嘛
Marcel! Where are you going with that disk?
不能再放上去  马塞尔
You are not putting that on again. Marcel!
如果你按那个按钮  你可有大麻烦了
If you press that button,you are in very, very big trouble.
你能相信罗斯刚刚那么混蛋吗
You believe what a jerk Ross was being?
-我懂  -他的好胜心最强了
- Yeah, I know. - He can get really competitive.
什么
What?
"你好水壶  我是莫妮卡  你好黑啊"
"Hello, kettle, This is Monica. You're black!"
拜托
Please!
我没像罗斯那么过分
I'm not as bad as Ross.
我抗议  "画图猜字"那次呢
I beg to differ. The Pictionary incident?
我不是故意的
That wasn't an incident.
我在做手势时盘子不慎从手里滑落了
I was gesturing and the plate slipped out of my hand.
-我有面试机会了  -不是吧  在哪
- I got an interview! - You're kidding! Where?
萨克斯第五大道精品店
Saks Fifth Avenue.
哦  瑞秋
Oh, Rachel!
这就像是母舰在呼唤你归队
It's like the mother ship is calling you home.
-是什么工作  -采购助理
- What's the job? - Assistant buyer.
我要靠购物...
I would be shopping!
来谋生了
For a living!
艾莉丝姑姑来了  她从五岁便开始玩牌
That's Aunt Iris. This woman's been playing poker since she was 5.
她说的每个字我们都得牢记在心
You've got to listen to every word she says.
托尼·兰德尔死了吗
ls Tony Randall dead?
-什么  没有吧  -现在说不定
- What? I don't think so. - He may be now.
-因为我好像开车撞到他了  -真的吗
- Because I think I hit him with my car. - My God, really?
不  唬你们的  这是第一课
No, that's bluffing. Lesson number one.
我告诉你们
Let me tell you something.
打扑克时听到的每个字都是狗屁
Everything you hear at a poker game is pure crap!
-耳环挺好看  -谢...
- Nice earrings. - Thank you.
坐吧  姑娘们
Girls, sit down.
艾莉丝姑姑  这是菲比  这是瑞秋
Aunt lris, this is Phoebe and Rachel.
听着  我停车要收费的  快点开始吧
Listen, I'm parked at a meter. Let's do it. Okay?
罗斯  求你了  我们能听点别的吗
Ross, could we please listen to anything else?
好吧
All right.
晚上我要遭报应了
I'm gonna pay for that tonight.
伙计们  猜猜看怎么了
Hi. Guys, guess what?
第五位牙医妥协了
The fifth dentist caved,
他们现在都推销"三叉戟"牌口香糖了吗
and now they're all recommending Trident?
不  是面试
No, the interview!
她喜欢我  她绝对非常喜欢我
She loved me! She absolutely loved me.
我们谈了能有两个半小时
We talked like two and a half hours.
我们对服饰的品味一致
We've the same taste in clothes.
我还和她的表妹一起去过夏令营
And I went to camp with her cousin.
这工作太完美了  我可以胜任
The job is perfect! I can do this.
太好了  太棒了
That's great! That's wonderful.
然后她给我讲了个超好笑的故事
Then she told the funniest story...
很好  行了  假设你讲完了我们笑完了
Great, you will tell us and we'll laugh.
玩牌吧
Let's play poker!
各位听好  我们谈过此事
Listen you guys, we talked about it
如果你们不想玩  我们完全了解
and if you don't wanna play, we completely understand
对  我们可以玩别的游戏
Yes, we can play some other game.
比如说看图猜字
Like, I don't know. Pictionary?
真好笑
Very funny.
但我们想再试一次打扑克  对吧姑娘们
But I think we'd like to give poker another try. Shall we, ladies?
没错  我想是的
Yes, I think we should.
瑞秋  需要我来洗牌吗
Rach. Do you want me to shuffle those?
不用了  没事  我想自己试试
No. That's okay, I'm gonna give it a go.
这样菲比欠7块5  莫妮卡欠10块
So Pheebs owes $7. 50. Monica owes $10.00.
瑞秋  你欠15块
And Rachel, you owe 15 big ones!
谢谢教我们"美女斜眼暗示法"
Thanks for teaching us Cross-Eyed Mary.
兄弟们  我们平时玩牌的时候也该试试
You guys, we gotta play that at our regular game.
给  这是我的7块5
All right, here's my $7.50.
不过我告诉你们  这钱已受到诅咒
But I think you should know that this money is cursed.
-什么  -我对它下了咒
- What? - I cursed it!
花这些钱的人会倒大霉
Now bad things will happen to the spender.
无所谓  我接受
That's alright, I'll take it.
我反正够倒霉的了
Bad things happen to me anyway.
这样的话  我还可以看场电影分散分散
This way, I can split them up with a movie.
现在只差格林牌扑克机欠了15块没给了
So that just leaves the big Greene poker machine, who owes 15.
男生都这副德行
It's so typical.
"我是男人  我有小鸡鸡"
"I'm a man! I have a penis!
"我得靠赢钱才能征服女人"
"I have to win money to exert my power over women!"
知道吗  这事没完
You know. This isn't over.
我们还要跟你们再战
We'll play you again.
我们大获全胜  你们一败涂地
And  we'll win, and you'll lose.
你们跪地求饶  我们仰天大笑
And you'll beg, and we'll laugh.
我们会赢走你们的每一分钱
And we'll take every last dime you have.
你们会永远恨死自己
And you'll hate yourselves forever!
你这有点给我拆台啊  莫妮卡
Kind of stepped on my point there, Mon.
姑娘们  你们想现在就把钱给我们吗
So, you gals wanna give us your money now?
这样我们就不必浪费时间
That way, we don't have to go through
装模作样地玩一场了
the formality of actually playing.
不  就这样
No, that's fine.
我倒要看看谁笑到最后  猴子男
We'll see who has the last laugh, monkey boy.
聊完了没  可以开始玩真的了吗
Done with chitchat? Ready for serious poker?
你们看  独眼杰克一直看着我
You guys, look! The one-eyed jack follows me wherever I go.
好  玩真的
Right. Serious poker.
-等下  你要上哪儿去  -卫生间
- Excuse me. Where are you going? - To the bathroom.
你想上厕所还是玩牌
Want to go to the bathroom or play poker?
我想上厕所
Go to the bathroom.
-好吧  我去订披萨  -不行
- Well, I'm gonna order a pizza. - No!
我还在等面试回信
I'm waiting to hear from that job.
他们的店9点关门  那时候再吃吧
The store closes at 9:00. Eat then.
行  那我就含块薄荷糖提神
That's fine. I'll just have a Tic Tac to hold me over.
来吧  辛辛那提玩法  下注吧
All right. Cincinnati. No blinds. Everybody,ante.
太好了
Yes!
或者不太好
Or no.
你的钱是我的了  格林
All right! Your money's mine, Greene.
你的裤门没拉  盖勒
Your fly's open, Geller.
你们知道我刚发现什么吗
You guys know what I just realized?
"杰克"就是把"扑克"中的"扑"换掉
Joker is poker with a "J"!
是巧合吗
Coincidence?
这么说"巧合"就是"茄盒"变过来的啊
That's jo-incidence with a "C"!
-菲比  -我不跟了
- Phoebe? - Yeah, I'm out.
-我跟  -我也跟
- I'm in. - Me too.
我也跟  你拿什么牌
Me too. What do you got?
你最好赶紧洗完澡  因为我要冲马桶了
You better hop out of the shower, because I got a flush.
行了  行了  行了
Well, well, well!
滚回来吧小子  因为我拿了四张六
Hop back in, bucko, because I got four sixes!
我有四张六  我赢了
I got four sixes! I won!
我真的赢了  天哪
I actually won! Oh, my God!
你们知道吗  我要把小罗斯堆起来
You know what? I'll make a little Ross pile.
我想这是罗斯的  那个也是罗斯的
I think that one was Ross'. And I think that one was Ross'.
你的钱都归了我  再也别想见到它
Well, I have got your money, and you'll never see it,
你的裤门还没拉
and your fly's still open,
我骗到你低头看
I made you look.
-我跟  -我肯定跟
- I'm in. - I couldn't be in-er.
莫妮卡  跟还是不跟
Monica, in or out?
我讨厌玩牌
I hate this game!
乔伊  你呢
Joey, your bet.
我输得像是个廉价妓女还被一个
I fold like a cheap hooker who got hit in the stomach...
满脸伤痕的胖子对着肚子踹了一脚
by a fat guy with sores on his face.
我不跟
I'm out.
-罗斯  -我确定跟
- Ross? - I'm very in.
-钱德勒  -绝对不跟
- Chandler? - Couldn't be more out.
我也一样  瑞秋
Me too. Rachel?
我不但跟而且还要加注
I will see you and I'll raise you.
如何  还想再浪费钱吗
What do you say, wanna waste another buck?
这回肯定不会  来吧  给我看牌
No, not this time. So, what did you have
-我不会说的  -给我看
- I'm not telling. - Show them.
-不  -给我看
- No. - Show them!
-把你的手拿开  -我约会时常常这样
- Get your hands out of there! - I've had dates like this.
天啊  你真是输不起的家伙
Boy, you really can't stand to lose, can you?
你的脸涨得好红
Your whole face is getting red.
太阳穴青筋毕露
Veins popping out of your temple!
而且这件上衣跟裤子一点不搭
Plus, that shirt doesn't really match those pants.
-首先  我不会输的  -你输定了
- First of all. I'm not losing. - You're definitely losing.
你好  瑞秋·格林
Hello. Rachel Greene.
不好意思  这是有关工作的电话
Excuse me. It's about the job!
芭芭拉  你好吗
Barbara, hi! How are you?
不  我理解
No, I understand.
不  我没事  快别这么说
Come on. No, I'm fine. Don't be silly. Yeah.
但如果还有其他职位缺人  请
But if anything else opens up, please
喂
Hello?
我很遗憾,瑞秋
Sorry, Rach.
工作机会肯定有的是
There's gonna be lots of other stuff.
好的
Okay.
玩到哪儿了
Where were we?
五张牌抽法
Five-card draw.
11点算大  大家下注
Jacks are better. Nothing wild. Everybody,ante.
-瑞秋  别再玩了  -要玩  下注
- Look, Rach, we don't have to do this. - Yes, we do.
-好吧  不跟  -不跟
- All right. Check. - Check.
-我跟5毛钱  -跟
- I'm in for 50 cents. - Call.
我跟
I'm in.
我跟你5毛
I see your 50 cents...
而且我要加5块钱
...and I raise you $5.
我以为5毛是上限
I thought it was a 50-cent limit.
我刚失去工作机会  所以想加5块
I just lost a job, I'd like to raise it $5.
各位有问题吗
Does anyone have a problem with that?
-当然没有  -没有  我们收牌
- Not at all. - No. We're out.
废柴
Loser?
-我收牌了  -你收牌是什么意思
- No, I fold. - What do you mean, you fold?
你不是说"一旦发牌  我就不是好人"吗
I thought that, "Once the cards are dealt, I'm not a nice guy."
还是只是信口胡说
Were you just full of it?
我跟
I'm in.
-要几张牌  -一张
- How many do you want? - One.
庄家两张
Dealer takes two.
-下多少  -我下2块
- What do you bet? - I bet $2.
我跟你2块
Okay. I see your $2...
再加你
...and I raise you...
20块
... 20.
我跟你20块
I see your $20...
再加到25块
... raise you $25.
跟你25块  莫妮卡  拿我的钱包来
I see your $25 and Monica, get my purse.
瑞秋  里面没钱
Rachel, there's nothing in it.
那就拿你的钱包来
Okay, then get me your purse.
-给你  祝你好运  -谢谢
- Here you go. Good luck! -Thank you.
跟你25块  再加
I saw your $25 and I raise you...
...7块
...seven.
是17块!
teen!
乔伊  我有点囊中羞涩
Joey, I'm a little shy.
没关系  罗斯  有什么问题可以问我
That's okay, Ross. You can ask me.
-要多少  -15块
- What do you need? - 15.
-这里有10块  -我这里有5块
- Here's 10. - I got 5.
-谢谢  -祝你好运
- Thank you. - Good luck.
再加十七块
I am calling your 17.
你拿什么牌
What do you got?
三张同点加一对
Full house.
败给你了
You got me.
-那确实很难赢  -我以为我们会赢
- That's tough to beat. - I thought we had it!
没有好牌就是没有好牌
When you don't have the cards, you don't have the cards.
瞧  她多开心
But look how happy she is.
-航空邮件  -飞机  机场  《75空难》
- Airmail. - Airplane. Airport. Airport '75!
《77空难》  《79空难》
Airport '77! Airport '79!
时间到
Time's up!
"再见了  小鸟"
Bye Bye Birdie!
那是小鸟
That's a bird?
那就是小鸟
That's a bird!
该我了
Okay, it's my turn.
开始
Go!
豆子  豆子
Bean! Bean!
生命中不能承受之轻
The Unbearable Lightness of Being!
答对了
That you get?
这样就能猜中
That you get?!